let questions = [
    {
        "question": "1)What is the capital city of United States of America?",
        "A":"New York",
        "B":"Washington",
        "C":"Chicago",
        "D":"Houston",
        "Answer":"B"
    },
    {
        "question": "2)What is the capital city of Russia?",
        "A":"St.Petersburg",
        "B":"Novgorod",
        "C":"Moscow",
        "D":"Krasnodar",
        "Answer":"C"
    },
    {
        "question": "3)What is the capital city of China?",
        "A":"Pekin",
        "B":"Beijing",
        "C":"Vuhan",
        "D":"Guangzhou",
        "Answer":"A"
    },
    {
        "question": "4)What is the capital city of Germany?",
        "A":"Frankfurt",
        "B":"Munchen",
        "C":"Berlin",
        "D":"Stuttgart",
        "Answer":"C"
    },
    {
        "question": "5)What is the capital city of England?",
        "A":"London",
        "B":"Manchester",
        "C":"Liverpool",
        "D":"Newcastle",
        "Answer":"A"
    },
    {
        "question": "6)What is the capital city of France?",
        "A":"Marseille",
        "B":"Lyon",
        "C":"Montpellier",
        "D":"Paris",
        "Answer":"D"
    },
    {
        "question": "7)What is the capital city of Canada?",
        "A":"Vancouver",
        "B":"Ottawa",
        "C":"Montreal",
        "D":"Toronto",
        "Answer":"B"
    },
    {
        "question": "8)What is the capital city of Japan?",
        "A":"Osaka",
        "B":"Kyoto",
        "C":"Tokyo",
        "D":"Yokohama",
        "Answer":"C"
    },
    {
        "question": "9)What is the capital city of Italy?",
        "A":"Naples",
        "B":"Milano",
        "C":"Venice",
        "D":"Rome",
        "Answer":"D"
    },
    {
        "question": "10)What is the capital city of Brazil?",
        "A":"Brasilia",
        "B":"Sao Paolo",
        "C":"Rio de Janeiro",
        "D":"Recife",
        "Answer":"A"
    },
    {
        "question": "11)What is the capital city of Netherlands?",
        "A":"Eindhoven",
        "B":"Rotterdam",
        "C":"Groningen",
        "D":"Amsterdam",
        "Answer":"D"
    },
    {
        "question": "12)What is the capital city of Greece?",
        "A":"Thessaloniki",
        "B":"Tripoli",
        "C":"Athens",
        "D":"Larissa",
        "Answer":"C"
    },
    {
        "question": "13)What is the capital city of South Korea?",
        "A":"Seoul",
        "B":"Busan",
        "C":"Ulsan",
        "D":"Daegu",
        "Answer":"A"
    },
    {
        "question": "14)What is the capital city of Spain?",
        "A":"Barcelona",
        "B":"Sevilla",
        "C":"Bilbao",
        "D":"Madrid",
        "Answer":"D"
    },
    {
        "question": "15)What is the capital city of Australia?",
        "A":"Brisbane",
        "B":"Canberra",
        "C":"Melbourne",
        "D":"Sydney",
        "Answer":"B"
    },
    {
        "question": "16)What is the capital city of Mexico?",
        "A":"Tijuana",
        "B":"Monterrey",
        "C":"Mexico City",
        "D":"Guadalajara",
        "Answer":"C"
    },
    {
        "question": "17)What is the capital city of Egypt?",
        "A":"Cairo",
        "B":"Alexandria",
        "C":"Giza",
        "D":"Suez",
        "Answer":"A"
    },
    {
        "question": "18)What is the capital city of Turkey?",
        "A":"Istanbul",
        "B":"Ankara",
        "C":"Izmir",
        "D":"Antalya",
        "Answer":"B"
    },
    {
        "question": "19)What is the capital city of India?",
        "A":"Mumbai",
        "B":"New Delhi",
        "C":"Bangalore",
        "D":"Jaipur",
        "Answer":"B"
    },
    {
        "question": "20)What is the capital city of Argentina?",
        "A":"Mendoza",
        "B":"Cordoba",
        "C":"Rosario",
        "D":"Buenos Aires",
        "Answer":"D"
    }
    ];